

Ashwini Jadhav

M.Com, CA Finalist

ashwinijadhav364@gmail.com

- +91 7774937524
- Mulund, Mumbai
- linkedin.com/in/ashwinijadhav364

SUMMARY

Worked with Jiten and Associates (CA firm) from July 2022 till February 2023.

Audit and Finance Assistant in M/s. Chhajed & Doshi, Dombivli – November 2013 to November 2016 (3 years)

Conducting a critical analysis of Trial Balance, Balance sheet involving ratio analysis, financial worthiness, and Preparation of Projections of financials for obtaining Business loans.

Finalization of books of Accounts of Companies as per applicable laws such as Maharashtra Co-operative Societies Act 1960, Companies Act 2013, and Banking Regulation Act 1949.

Replying to Income tax, and GST notices.

As a CA finalist, I am eager to leverage my skills and knowledge to contribute to the success of your organization. I am committed to continuous learning and professional growth, staying updated with the latest industry trends and regulations.

PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATION

Institute of Charted Accountants of India (ICAI):

Appeared for CA Final Group 2 (May 2023), IPCC (Both Groups) Cleared

ADVANCE CERTIFICATE IN FINANCIAL SERVICE (Diploma in Finance)

EXPERIENCE

TAX Analyst - Jiten and Associates (CA firm) - Jul 2022 to Feb 2023

- Monthly book closures, Preparation of Monthly/ Quarterly Financial Statements/
- Annual Financial Statements & MIS Reports
- Responsible for all Direct & Indirect tax compliances including GST, TDS, Tax Audits, GST Audit, PTEC/PTRC Compliances for clients
- Responsible for completion of Internal & Statutory audit in given time and Coordination with Auditors

Article Assistants M/s. Chhajed & Doshi, Dombivli - Nov 2013 to Nov 2016

- Filling of Income Tax Returns of Individual/Company.
- Direct firsthand in VAT Audit, Tax Audit, Stock Audit, and Internal Control Mechanisms of various companies.
- Statutory audit of various Banks & Co-Operative Societies, Internal Audit of Banks
 & Private companies
- Supervising the preparation of monthly financials, Evaluation of projects based on Cost-benefit analysis to arrive at commercial and financial feasibility.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Financial Reporting and Analysis
- Auditing and Assurance
- Tax Planning and Compliance
- Budgeting and Forecasting
- Regulatory Compliance
- Internal Controls and Process Improvement
- Financial Modelling and Analysis
- Team Leadership and Collaboration
- Excellent Problem-Solving and Decision-Making Abilities

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- MS Office & Advance Excel
- Tally ERP 9, Tally 7.2
- Winman, ClearTax, WinTDS

LANGGUAGES

English

Marathi

Hindi

PERSONAL DETAILS

• Gender: Female

Marital status: Married

• DOB: 21-Mar-1993

FREELANCER EXPERIENCE

- Basic Accounting of Private limited companies
- GST Returns
- Income Tax Returns
- Coach for Audit and Law (CMA Inter) subjects